Yuji, you're a strong kid,
so try to help others.
In my Ten Shadows technique, only two
demon dogs are granted to the Yuji.
user at first.
The other shikigami aren't granted to
the user until they finish subjugating
them.
The user must continue subjugating
each one to increase the shikigami
available to them until they're finally
able to command all ten shikigami.
You done yet?
You're really strong, just
like the girl I fought earlier.
So strong and yet still so young.
You're all beat up, yet you give
me no openings to get close.
Although, with all that blood, I won't
even have to do anything else to you.
Ah.
Thing is, this subjugation can
be done with multiple people.
Although, conducting the subjugation with
multiple people will void it afterward.
Which means the ritual becomes pointless
because the technique gets nullified.
Still, even though it's pointless,
it has its uses for a sorcerer.
Who's making all that
noise? Pretty flashy.
To continue.
Now, while the Shikigami can't be
used without first subjugating it,
And the user can summon
them as many times as
necessary for the purpose
of subjugating them.
Are you saying that...
In all of sorcerer history,
there's never been anyone who's
managed to subjugate this one.
Do you know why the Gojo clan and
the Zenin clan are on bad terms?
I didn't know they were on bad terms.
On the worst terms.
Sparks have been constantly
flying ever since the Eido era.
Or was it the Keicho era?
I forget which one.
But the heads of the clans at the time
got serious during a spectated match,
and they killed each other.
Who headed the clans back then?
The Gojo family had someone like me,
who had both the Six Eyes
and the Limitless technique.
The Zenin clan had someone with
the same technique as you, Megumi.
The Ten Shadows technique.
You understand what I'm getting at, right?
That doesn't mean I can become a
sorcerer who's stronger than you.
I imagine the head of the clan used
this in much the same way back then.
With this treasure, I summon...
Hmm?
Sukuna?
Urgent business.
I see.
It won't be much longer now,
before I'm completely free.
Do not neglect your preparation.
See you later, Uralme.
Sir, I shall be waiting for you.
He tricked me.
He started that subjugation ritual.
He's forcing me to participate
in the damn thing with him.
A grip sword.
Divergent, the Divine General. Mahoraga.
See you later, yeah.
Sorry, Itadori.
Hey, you damn bastard!
I'll be dying first.
Let me see your best shot
Wait
Oh fuck You!
Damn it!
Wake up!
You shitty fuck!
The technique of the
curse user Haruta Shigemo
erases life's little daily
miracles from his memory.
and stores them up.
That stalk manifests as the
markings under his eyes,
and when he is faced with
a threat to his life,
one miracle is released.
However, he is completely
unaware of this fact himself.
Suspended animation, huh?
Interesting.
So saving this piece of trash
really was the right move.
He'd probably suck this thing into
the subjugation ritual along with him.
Once this loser dies, the
ritual will be complete,
and then Megumi Fushiguro
will die as well.
Don't die yet.
There are things I need you
to do for me before that.
Huh?
Oh no... Quiet.
For Megumi Fushiguro to survive,
I'll have to defeat the Shikigami as an
outsider and nullify his subjugation ritual.
Now then, time to have a little taste.
Dismantle.
That sword.
It's the sword of extermination.
A specialized blade to
combat cursed spirits.
It's packed with the same positive energy
generated by a reverse curse technique.
If I was a cursed spirit, that would
have eliminated me with the first blow.
Disgusting.
Come at me!
Let's go.
Oh.
Now, what was that all about?
No way. No way.
Oh, my God.
That felt odd.
Again, again!
Oh, my God.
Cursed energy.
Now you've done it!
You can see it, Mahoraga!
You can see my curse technique!
Let's go.
I knew it!
You're similar to Yamata no Orochi!
You follow my slices, and
attack with cursed energy.
Both started happening after that
great wheel of yours revolved.
The incantation of sacred
treasures and that great
wheel both represent
perfect cycles and harmony,
which suggests that the Shikigami's ability
is to adapt to anything and everything.
It's the ultimate elite throw
in rock, paper, scissors.
You might have had a
chance to defeat me if
I was still in the state
I was in back then.
Now you've fascinated
me, Megumi Fushiguro!
Domain Expansion
Malevolent Shrine
Sukuna's Domain.
Malevolent Shrine.
Unlike other domains, it does not cut
out a separate space with a barrier.
Manifesting an innate domain
without sealing it in a barrier
is like trying to paint a picture
in the air without a canvas.
It is a truly divine feat.
To top it off, by adding a pact to
allow its victims a path of escape,
it vastly increases the
range of its guaranteed
hit effect to a maximum
of a 200 meter radius.
Though out of consideration for
its effect on Megumi Fushiguro,
he has currently restrained the effect to
a 140 meter radius limited to the surface.
Anything nope no signal
same yeah but I don't
think we need to worry about that anymore?
Huh remember the guy with the
megaphone I'm pretty sure he should be
Sukuna's slices are comprised of two types
cleave attacks things
with cursed energy in
the range of his guaranteed hit effect,
Dismantle attacks things
without cursed energy.
Both
attack all targets relentlessly
until Malevolent Shrine is gone.
The only sure way to defeat
Maharagan is to slaughter it with the
first use of an attack before it can adapt.
Klee would have fulfilled
those conditions,
but that wouldn't
necessarily hold true if it
It had adapted to slices in general,
rather than to dismantle it.
Maharaga's regeneration
will soon be complete.
Open.
What the hell are you looking at?
Be gone.
Excuse me!
My luck never runs out!
I'll see you another day!
I survived!
Shigemo's stock of miracles had run
out in his battle against Kento Nanami.
Oh, it's nearly time.
Fushiguro!
No.
I just saw Itadori for a
moment. No. Was it Tsukuna?
You little brat.
Be sure to savor this feeling forever.
I don't know.
Die!
Only me!
Right now!
I love you baby.
I love
you
baby.
I love you baby.
I will not be able to give you a chance!
If I was over me, I will be able to.
It should make you cry,
you're a rendezvous?
I may get so much you are my special.
I have to go, I have to fight!
It should make you cry,
you're a rendezvous?
Otherwise, I'll just be a murderer.
Thank you.
If you want to choose the right
world, it's easy to choose.
It's easy to say that you don't want to
use
the wrong place.
I want you to believe that I
want you to believe, right?
It's always the same as your pain.
The night that you have
to be with me is you.
Just be by yourself.
This has gotten really bad.
I'll count prime numbers to calm down.
One, two, three, uh, nine.
You missed five and seven.
Next time, right and wrong.
You'll turn into a panda
if you don't watch.
You really are an animal